

Post DNB Neurosurgery 18 Months of Experience Indraprastha Apollo Hospital New Delhi, India

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name Dr Aditendraditya Singh Bhati

Date of birth 6th May 1978

Nationality Indian

Address Sector B-10, H.No: 7216, Vasant Kunj, New Delhi,

India. Pin – 110070

Languages Known English, Hindi, Telugu & Nepali

Contact Details Mobile: +919999879997

Email: adityaneurosurgery@yahoo.com

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

- ➤ Diplomate of National Board (DNB) Neurosurgery (2016)
- ➤ M,B.B.S, Kathmandu Medical college,

Kathmandu University, Nepal (2004)

PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

M.N.A.M.S - Member of the National Academy of Medical Sciences

I.M.A - Indian Medical Association

D.M.C - Delhi Medical Association

N.S.I - Neurological Society of India

N.S.S.I - Neurological surgeons Society of India

CLINICAL APPOINTMENTS

PRESENT:

ATTENDING CONSULTANT

Department of Neurosurgery Indraprastha Apollo Hospital New Delhi, India

(15th February 2016 – Till date)

PREVIOUS APPOINTMENTS:

NEUROSURGERY RESIDENCY (13th Feb 2010 to 12th Feb 2016)

Department of Neurosurgery Indraprastha Apollo Hospital New Delhi, India

Phone No: 0091-11-29871090

RESIDENT, NEUROSURGERY

(12th Sep 2006 to 12th Feb 2010)

Department of Neurosurgery Indian Spinal Injuries Centre New Delhi, India.

Phone No: 0091-11-42255225

RESIDENT

(16th Aug 2005 to 6th Sep 2006)

Department of General & Allied surgery Mediciti Hospital Hyderabad, India.

Phone No: 0091-11-23231111

OBSERVERSHIP

(24th Feb 2004 to 15th Aug 2005)

Department of General & Allied surgery
Mediciti Hospital
Hyderabad, India.
Phone No: 0091-11-23231111

Phone No. 0091-11-23231111

INTERNSHIP

Kathmandu medical college & Teaching hospital Kathmandu, Nepal

(15th Feb 2003 to 15th Feb 2004)

The Rotation during internship was as below

Community Medicine 3 months Surgery & Orthopedics 2 months Medicine 2 months Obstetrics & Gynecology 2 months 15 days **Pediatrics Psychiatry** 15 days Dermatology 15 days Forensic Medicine 15 days **ENT** 15 days Ophthalmology 15 days

RESEARCH & PUBLICATIONS

- ➤ Bhati AS et al. SK. Recurrent granular cell tumor: a case report and review of literature. **J Spine Surg** 2017. doi: 10.21037/jss.2017.08.01
- ➤ Incidental, Bilateral Elongated Styloid Process in Head Injury A Case Report and Review of Literature, **International Journal of Science and Research**. https://www.ijsr.net/archive/v6i8/v6i8.php, Volume 6 Issue 8, August 2017, 1062 1064, #ijsrnet
- ➤ Combined use of Hyperbaric Oxygen and Stem Cell Therapy in management of severe traumatic brain injury" A case report: Accepted for publication in **Indian Journal of applied research**.
- ➤ Mobile Schwannoma of high cervical cord: A case Report and review of literature Accepted for publication in **International Annals of Medicine**.
- ➤ THESIS During DNB Training of Neurosurgery:
 A prospective study of patients with diffuse axonal injury

NATIONAL PRESENTATIONS

- ➤ Deep brain stimulation patients for Parkinson's disease, 15th Biannual conference of Indian society for Stereotactic & Functional Neurosurgery (STEREOCON 2017), September 2017, Chandigarh, India.
- ➤ Granular Cell Tumor A case report, Delhi Neurological Association meet, May 2017, New Delhi, India.
- Recurrent Tentorial Meningioma and Ascitis, 5th Annual conference, Neurosurgical Surgeons' Society of India (NSSI Annual meet, March April 2016), Srinagar-Kashmir, India.
- ➤ Cranial Interdural Tubercular Abscess, Delhi Neurological Association Meet, April 2014, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Poster Presentation: Subarachnoid Hemorrhage mimicking as Myocardial Infarction A case report, 3rd Annual conference of Neurosurgical Surgeons' Society of India (NSSI Annual meet, Feb-Mar 2014), Rishikesh, India.
- ➤ "Our experience of epilepsy surgery", Biannual conference of Indian society for Stereotactic & Functional Neurosurgery (STEREOCON 2013), September 2013, New Delhi.
- ➤ Intracranial Deep Seated Lesions, Delhi Neurological Association meet, April 2013, New Delhi.

WORKSHOPS & CONFERENCES ATTENDED

- ➤ Biannual Conference, Indian society for stereotactic & Functional Neurosurgery, September 2017, Post Graduate Institute, Chandigarh, India.
- ➤ Annual conferences of Neurological Surgeons' Society of India, 2014, 2015 & 2016.
- ➤ 64th Annual National Conference and Epilepsy Surgery Workshop, Neurological society of India, December 2015, Hyderabad, India.
- ➤ WFNS Skull base Neuroendoscopy Workshop, 25th-26th November, 2015.
- ➤ Cadaveric dissection course, Cadaver Training & Research facility, 7th -8th November, 2015, JPNA Trauma Centre, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Neurosurgery Skills Training Program, 17th August to 17th September 2015, AIIMS, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Instructional Course on Peripheral Nerves and Brachial Plexus Injury, April 2015, Sir Ganga Ram Hospital, New Delhi, India.
- Microneurovascular Training by Ethicon, Delhi, 22nd February 2015.
- ➤ Short Term Training at Cadaver Training & Research Facility, 7th & 8th February 2015, JPNA Trauma Centre, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Cadaveric hands-on Dissection Course in Neurosurgery, February 2015, AIIMS, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Biannual Conference, Indian Society for Stereotactic & Functional Neurosurgery, September 2013, Indraprastha Apollo Hospital, New Delhi, India.

- ➤ Cadaveric hands-on Workshop on Endoscopic Endonasal extended Skull-base Surgery/Cervical Spinal Instrumentation & Brachial Plexus Exposure by NSSI, July 2013, SMS Medical College, Jaipur, India.
- ➤ 61st Annual National Conference, Neurological society of India December 2012, AIIMS, New Delhi, India.
- Functional Neurosurgery and Brain mapping, October 2012, Indraprastha Apollo Hospital, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ AIIMS Microneurosurgery workshops 2011 & 2012 New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Live Neurosurgery and Neurointervention Workshop, October 2011, AIIMS, New Delhi, India.
- ➤ Joint 13th Annual Conference, Delhi Neurological Association (DNACON-2011), January 2011, New Delhi, India.

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I was drawn towards the neurosurgical discipline during my M,B.B.S schooling. I did my neurosurgical training and learnt the basics under Prof. AK Banerji, Prof. Ravi Bhatia, Dr VP Singh, Dr Ashish K Shrivastav & Dr Sudheer Tyagi at Indraprastha Apollo Hospital, New Delhi, India. This was supplemented by the neurologists, neuropathologists and neuroradiologists in the non-surgical aspect of neurosciences. During the training and thereafter for last 18 months, my spectrum, repertoire and expertise of neurosurgical operation and management is being gradually expanded under the watchful eyes of my senior colleagues.

REFEREES

• **Prof. RAVI BHATIA**, MS, M.Ch (Neurosurgery)

Emeritus Senior Consultant Neurosurgery
Former Professor & Head of Neurosurgery, AIIMS, New Delhi
Sr. Consultant, Department of Neurosurgery
Indraprastha Apollo Hospital,

Sarita Vihar, New Delhi 110076. INDIA.

Phone: (M) 00-91- 9810058520 Email - ravibhatia1938@gmail.com

• Dr. ASHISH K SHRIVASTAV, MS, M.Ch (Neurosurgery)

Sr. Consultant, Department of Neurosurgery Indraprastha Apollo Hospital, Sarita Vihar, New Delhi 110076. INDIA.

Phone: (M) 00-91- 9811111277 Email - ashish1163@msn.com

• **Dr. SUDHEER K TYAGI**, MS, M.Ch (Neurosurgery)

Sr. Consultant, Department of Neurosurgery Indraprastha Apollo Hospital, Sarita Vihar, New Delhi 110076. INDIA.

Phone: (M) 00-91- 9810082721 Email - sudheerktyagi@gmail.com